Morevna Project...
...in association with "Adamant" Art School of Gorno-Altaisk...
presents
"Falcon", "Falcon", respond. This is "Hawk". What's your status?
Hey officer, can I help you somehow?
Stay away, stay away!
I am a government agent!
I know, I know...
And I am the owner of this mansion.
Episode 3: Underground
Ah, Marya Morevna, I just don't get it. We aren't that rich...
...but they are coming here like bees to a...
...honeypot!
I am not a bee, I am a "Hawk".
Spread your wings, Hawk.
But it seems like you're having fun.
Of course I am!
But still, why did you drop my favorite toolbox on him?
I just can't figure out what you did to them if they're after you so much...
I have no idea.
Going somewhere?
I am going to a biker party, and I won't be back until tomorrow.
Dinner on plate, firewood in shed, dog food under sink...
Do we have dogs here?
...in case of a power outage, turn on the electric generator and don't forget to restart the air defense system.
Here are the keys to all of the doors in the mansion.
Feel free to go anywhere, but don't touch this key and don't unlock the door.
But why?
Just don't!
Well, bye...
So dear, now I can have some fun with you then.
Hm, it seems this lovely evening is in danger.
Stay here, I'll be right back.
Caption on the door: "Cellar"
Aha, here it is!
What?
Could it be...
...feel free to go anywhere, but don't touch this key...
Hey, is anybody here?
There is something wrong with your engine here.
Damn you…
Ah? Who is it?
Come on...
My name is Ivan Tsarevich... and I am very good at fixing things.
Inside...
There...
The framework is quite unusual. It will be a challenge to get inside.
So, let's start!
Yes...
Excellent...
Well done.
Certainly, you've got talent...
This is not the hardest one...
Still, it's quite strange that it's so tricky to open this thing...
Well, that's all.
Open Sesame!
What's up? You are almost there!
I don't know... there seems to be some piece of paper here... I'm going to remove it now.
Oh, no...