The Story of Mim and Tiger
Once upon a time, there lived a Mim.
He worked in a zoo.
One day...
...right in the middle of his performance...
...the director of the zoo approached him and invited into his office.
Calm down kid...
Listen...
Yesterday a monkey died in the zoo.
She was everyone’s favorite...
Replace her. We’ll pay you well!
Mim accepted the deal.
He had never had a job like that (or better).
He got delicious food, fame...
Above all — He did absolutely nothing.
In a week he noticed...
...interest to him had fallen down.
Now the audience were interested in a tiger from the next cage.
That hurt Mim deeply.
So then, he climbed to the tiger and started to tease him.
The tiger didn't like that, of course.
More and more people were coming to watch the show.
The zoo’s networth had grown up...
Mim got a pay rise.
Day after day he climbed to the tiger...
Tiger roared...
Audience applauded.
But one wonderful day…
Death, awful and imminent, was inexorably approaching him.
Mim screamed.
Tsch... Shut up!
Or you want us both to lose the job?