Hello friends!
On your screen, you can see a clip from the "Pepper & Carrot" motion comic
And in this video course, I'll teach you how to create such an animation.
You can download files for this lesson by following relevant links in description of this video.
If you purchased the full course, then you can find them included in the archive.
For the further work we need...
GIMP...
and "Blender"...
...with the "COA Tools" addon installed for both.
Let's start with installing the COA Tools Addon in GIMP.
Open the downloaded COA Tools folder
And copy the file located in the "GIMP" folder.
Then, go to the GIMP settings folder...
...and find the "Plugins" folder.
Paste the file we copied from COA Tools.
Make sure that the addon is executable.
Done.
The COA Tools addon allows GIMP to export every layer into separate pictures...
...as a PNG.
The addon also exports additional information about the placement of each layer.
Now, let's open our ORA file in GIMP.
Here is the character you saw in beginning of this video.
Notice, it is separated into layers...
...so that we can animate it.
For some parts you can see several versions exist.
For example, there are different variants of mouth here.
Such parts should be grouped together. The grouping tells the export plugin to treat those parts specially and allow to switch them during animation process.
For all other other cases however,
the parts should not be grouped.
So, let's start exporting.
Click "File"...
...then "Export to CoaTools".
Next, enter the name and path of the scene.
Done.
Let's check the result.
As you can see, the addon created a folder where we can find all our layers separated.
Also, there is a file with the .JSON extension.
This file stores information about coordinates of each layer.
We will need it to import our scene into Blender.
But first, we need to install CoaTools addon for Blender.
Just like in the beginning, start by openning the downloaded CoaTools folder.
Open the "Blender" folder inside.
Here we can see another folder - "coa_tools".
We need to make a ZIP archive of it.
Done.
Next, let's run Blender.
Go to "File"...
User Preferences...
And find the Add-ons tab.
Then click on the "Install from File" button.
Select the "coa_tools" ZIP archive.
After that, find the installed Add-on.
Put a tick before it.
And click Save User Settings.
Done.
If you've done everything correct, then in T-menu...
(the one which is opened by 't' key)
...the "Cutout animation" tab will appear.
Let's import our scene".
Delete the start scene...
Now, you need to snap your cursor to the center.
To do that, you need to press the key combination "Shift+S"...
...and choose "Cursor to Center".
Then, go to "Cutout animation" in T-menu.
And click on "Create new Sprite".
A plain axes object is created. Our scene will be linked to it.
Now, press the "Import Sprites" button
And choose the .JSON file, which was created earlier.
Voilà!
We've successfully imported our scene into Blender.
Everything is in its place!